[Music] all the press we're less that kid
[音乐]所有媒体我们都不是那个孩子
just exploded a bomb [Music]
刚炸了炸弹[音乐]
les 400 coups, said henri georges clouzot, is a film that positively affected me
henri georges clouzot说les 400政变是一部对我产生积极影响的电影
packed the most sensitive film I have seen since the war as to
收录了我自战争以来看过的最敏感的电影
the appreciation of jean cocteau it was no less laudatory i have
吉恩·科克托（Jean cocteau）的欣赏我同样赞美
never been so upset in the cinema [Music]
在电影院里从来没有这么难过[音乐]
gavin and yes more severe for society than even an indictment
加文，对社会而言，甚至比起诉更为严厉
jova and georges sadoul will write in french letters
乔瓦（Jova）和乔治（Georges Sadoul）将用法语写信
emotion seizes you it continues to tighten your throat for hours
情绪抓住了你，它持续收紧你的喉咙几个小时
who follow this revelation a great talent us and is that I greet with
谁跟随了这个启示，我们是一个伟大的才华，我向他致以诚挚的问候。
admiration and respectful friendship
钦佩和尊重的友谊
[Music] at the worlds antoine dumas on bad
[音乐]在世界上安托万杜马节上表现不佳
time strings that she both tonight for what with my father a story
今晚她俩在一起跟我父亲讲故事的时间
engaging without spectacular rebellion as evidenced by paul guyot in
保罗·古耶特（Paul Paul Guyot）在
France evening the film won quite simply because
这部电影在法国当晚获胜的原因很简单，因为
how beautiful is everything that goes without sentences to the end of the truth
没有句子到真相的尽头，一切都是多么的美丽
his parents say you lie all the time no i miss every now and then
他的父母说你一直在撒谎，不，我时不时地想念
what sometimes i will tell them things that are the truth not believe me then
有时我会告诉他们什么是事实，那就不相信我
I prefer to say simple words [Music]
我喜欢说简单的话[音乐]
about this film everything was so spontaneously and so generously expressed
关于这部电影，一切都如此自发，如此慷慨地表达
until now that nothing can be added to it, his works appear to be the
直到现在什么都没加，他的作品似乎是
big victory of a wager held by this young is fierce film critic
这个年轻人的赌注的巨大胜利是激烈的电影评论家
who dared to face the danger of reciprocity by becoming in turn
敢于反过来面对互惠的危险
director this film will have written to jacqueline michel in the
这部电影的导演将写信给杰奎琳·米歇尔（Jacqueline Michel），
parisien libéré truffaut did better than a masterpiece a rigorous work
parisienlibérétruffaut的表现胜过严谨的杰作
vibrant beautiful and sincere that tears our heart gently tenderly
充满生机的美丽和真诚，温柔地泪流满面
without cries and without grandiloquence the 400 blows have for main star jean
没有哭声，也没有大胆的话，主明星吉恩的400次打击
pierre laud he reveals to us an astonishing talent in
皮埃尔·劳德（piere laud），他向我们展现了惊人的才能
the role of the terrible kid in this film patrick au fait qu air mourier albert
可怕的孩子在这部电影中的角色
remy and attic guy yes the search for the absolute drove you right rate
雷米（Remy）和阁楼小伙子是的，对绝对物品的搜索使您获得正确的价格
zero or friends for others less familiar with balzac I would say he
零或其他不熟悉balzac的人的朋友，我会说他
it is a dark affair anyway after this blow there with my
无论如何，这与我的打击之后是一件黑暗的事情
parents I have to disappear you understand
父母我要消失你明白
[Music] yes
[音乐]是的
Yes
是的
[Music]
[音乐]